Name Thor Wessel Lindberg

Address Reykjavík, Iceland
Email thor@lindberg.is

Website lindberg.is

GitHub github.com/thorlindberg
LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/thorlindberg



Profile

MSc.IT. specialized in UX Design, with a cross-disciplinary background in medical science, information technology and user-centred design. As an experienced Consultant in the finance and government sector, I have gained extensive experience on meeting and presenting to clients, planning project timelines and tasks, and continuously delivered on time.

Interests

In my spare time I enjoy building software to meet people's needs, experimenting with new technologies, and traveling throughout the U.S. to network with others in the tech sector.

Experience

08/2022 - 12/2023

Netcompany

IT Consultant

- · Allocated in the intersection of finance and government systems.
- · Responsible for client contact, mediating meetings, status reporting, managing project.
- · Analyzed and documented existing business processes on 2 projects for 2 clients.
- Analyzed IT-infrastructure and digital transformation strategy on 2 projects for 2 clients.
- · Contributed to new Java source code on 1 project for 1 client.

10/2021 - 07/2022

National Special Crime Unit

IT-Administrative Student

- · Managed users of webportal and provided direct support.
- · Authored software documentation and website content.

08/2021 - 06/2022

IT University of Copenhagen

Teaching Assistant

- · Assisted with teaching course material for 1 course in UX design.
- Assisted with assignments for 1 course in Python and 1 course in JavaScript and MQTT.

08/2021 - 01/2022

Domino's Pizza

Shift Leader

• Responsible for closing store, delegating work, managing cash, and primary pizza baker.

Education

08/2020 - 06/2022

Master of Science in Digital Design, IT University of Copenhagen

Thesis: Type-Extensible Objection Notation (TXON)

• Explorative design for embedding typeset objects within the limitations of JSON.

Relevant courses:

· Mobile development with Expo / React Native, UX Design, Advanced Design Processes.

08/2017 - 07/2020

Bachelor of Science in Health Informatics, Copenhagen University

Thesis: Tools for caretakers of stroke victims

 Qualitative analysis to determine potential low-cost digital solutions for caretakers of stroke victims, within economic constraints of the Danish healthcare system.

Relevant courses:

 Statistics, Mathematical Modelling, Medical Image Analysis, IT Security, Interaction Design, Programming for Biosciences, Human Anatomy, Physiology and Diseases.

08/2016 - 06/2017

Diploma of Culinary Arts, Copenhagen Hospitality College

Relevant courses: small-business management and nutrition science.

Certificates

0?/2024 — 0?/2024 Data Structures and Algorithms, University of California San Diego

Courses in advanced data structures and implementation of algorithms.

0?/2024 — 0?/2024 **Google UX Design**, Google

Courses in design processes, design research, prototyping, and building dynamic interfaces.

Skills

Development React, React Native, JavaScript, TypeScript, Swift, SwiftUI, UIKit, Java, MATLAB, Azure, Git

Data analysis Python, NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib

Design Figma, components, variants, interactive flows, auto layout

Language Fluent in English and Danish. Beginner at German and Icelandic

Published

App Store Áfangastaður - Explore Iceland, apps.apple.com/app/id6466740299

Application for finding destinations by category in Iceland.

Package react-native-modal-provider, npmjs.com/react-native-modal-provider

Provides a context for displaying React nodes in a modal above the wrapped nodes.